question_data = {"response_code":0,"results":[{"category":"Geography","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Alaska is the largest state in the United States.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Cartoon & Animations","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Bill Cipher in the show 'Gravity Falls' is the good guy.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"The color orange is named after the fruit.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"No Game No Life first aired in 2014.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"The PlayStation was originally a joint project between Sega and Sony that was a Sega Genesis with a disc drive.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"In the 'Toaru Kagaku no Railgun' anime,  espers can only reach a maximum of level 6 in their abilities.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Film","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"In the movie The Revenant, DiCaprio's character hunts down the killer of his son.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Film","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"George Lucas directed the entire original Star Wars trilogy.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Television","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"In 'Star Trek', Klingons are aliens.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"A pasodoble is a type of Italian pasta sauce.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]}]}
